Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES, 1921-80 (Part 1)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES II. CLASSIFIED FILES (part 1)
  - CFPPD
    - Interest on Surplus Center Funds, 1974 (Box 53, Folder 82)
    - Job Description Assistant to CEO for Affiliate, Center Coordination, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 83)
    - Kellogg Grant, Technical Assistance 1968-71 (Box 53, Folder 84)
    - Means of Including PPWP Headquarters Costs in Affiliate Government Grants, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 85)
    - (Background Material) Means of Including PPWP Headquarters in Government Grants, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 86)
    - Minutes of Planning Consultants Meeting, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 87)
    - Monthly Project Status Report, 1969, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 88)
    - Monthly Reports, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 89)
    - National Center for Family Planning PD, New Careers, 1968-69 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - NY State Health Planning Commission Survey Conducted by the CFPPD, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Program Handbook, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Project Development Program Report to the Ford Foundation on Grant no. 66-453, 1968-69 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - National, Program Expansion Committee Correspondence, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Proposal, National Technical Assistance Center for Development FP Programs, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Center for Family Planning Program Development, Memos, 1969-74 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - National, Program Planning and Development, Memos to Affiliates, 1964-68 (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
    - Progress Report to the Sloan Foundation, The Planning Unit, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Proposal Rf. PCFR 72-10 to HEW, 1970-72 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Proposed Title 1V-A Regulations, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Overview by County of Need for Subsidized Family Planning Services, Design and Procedures, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Reasons for Semi-Independent Identity, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Relationship Between CFPPD & PPFA, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Report for the Record, 1968-70 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Program Planning & Development Report to the Ford Foundation on Grant 66-453, 1968 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Resolution Passed by PPFA Board in Support of the Center, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - San Francisco Community Meeting, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Short Term Costs & Benefit Study, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - State Medical Assistance Programs, 1967 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Status of Family Planning Proposals to Office of Economic Opportunity, 1966 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Support to Affiliates Redraft Edc. 5 Point Statement, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Survey Instruments Relating to FY1971 County Study, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - 1969 Survey of Hospital Family Planning Services Questionnaire Only, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Survey AGI Agencies Providing Family Planning Services, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - CFPPD Planning Unit Table & Presentation SMSA Studies, 1970 (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - National, Center for Family Planning PD Technical Assistance, 1968-73 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - STAFF
    - CFPPD Dryfoos, Joy, Correspondence & Memos, 1969-74 (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - ROSOFF, JEANNIE
      - AGI Washington, DC, Rosoff, J., Appointment Vice President for Governmental Affairs, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - CFPPD
    - Washington, DC
      - The Appropriations Process, undated (Box 54, Folder 31)
      - Basic Information About Federal Funding, Rosoff, Jeannie, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 32)
      - "The Comprehensive National Health Insurance Act," Kennedy S. 3286 & Mills HR 13870, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - AGI Washington, DC, History, Functions, Objectives of the Washington Office, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - CFPPD
    - Washington, DC
      - History of Family Planning Legislation, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 35)
      - Impoundment Case Memorandum & Order, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - Alan Guttmacher Institute Washington, DC, Rosoff, Jeannie Leases, 1976-77 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - CFPPD Washington, DC, Minority Report, Conscience Clause, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - AGI Washington, DC, "National Issues" Kit, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - CFPPD
    - Washington, DC
      - The Need for Additional Funds, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 40)
      - The New Health Maintenance Organization Law & Family Planning, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 41)
      - Rosoff, Population & Family Planning, US Government 1942-69 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - AGI Washington, DC, AGI Time Reporting System for the Washington Office, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - CFPPD
    - Rosoff, Suit Filed for Family Planning Impounded Funds, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Washington, DC, Summary of the Project Development Unit, Activities for Fiscal Year, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - AGI
    - Washington, DC
      - Rosoff, Jeannie, Director, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 46)
      - Proposal for 1978 Washington Office Agreement, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - CFPPD
    - Washington, DC
      - Table of Federal Resources to Finance Family Planning Services 1972 (Box 54, Folder 48)
      - Status of Family Planning Legislation
        - 1974 (Box 54, Folder 49)
        - 1975-81 (Box 54)
  - The Alan Guttmacher Institute, Jeannie I. Rosoff, Washington, DC Washington Memo, 1979-80 (Box 54, Folder 50-51)
  - CFPPD Washington, DC, Rosoff, J., Editorial HEW Reorganizing: Setting the Stage for Further Cutting, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Rosoff, Jeannie
    - Alan Guttmacher Institute, Washington DC, Memos, 1975-78 (Box 54, Folder 53-56)
    - CFPPD Washington, DC, Memos 1970-74 (Box 54, Folder 57-61)
    - National Headquarters, Washington, DC, Memos 1966-69 (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - CFPPD Washington, DC, Organization Outline for Statewide Public Affairs Committees, 1972 (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - Rosoff, Jeannie
    - National Headquarters, Washington, DC, 1965-69 (Box 54, Folder 64)
    - Washington, DC, Director Public Policy
      - 1970-74 (Box 54, Folder 65)
      - 1975-78 (Box 54)
    - Washington, DC, Public Affairs Network & Public Affairs, 1969-71 (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - CFPPD
    - Washington, DC
      - Public Affairs Workshop, 1971 (Box 54, Folder 67)
      - Questionnaire Survey, Funding Patterns PPWP Affiliates Public Services, 1970-71 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - Government Grant Percentages of PPWP Affiliates Total Income, 1970 Estimated 1971 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - AGI Washington, DC, Questionnaires, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - "Towards a Family Planning and Population Agency" (Rosoff Paper), 1969 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Washington, DC Headquarters Conference at Cumberland Falls, KY, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - CFPPD Washington, DC, CFPPD Strategy in the Development of Statewide Family Planning Programs, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Washington, DC Data Retrieval System for TA Assigned Family Planning Projects, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - CFPPD
    - Funded Grants, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Washington, DC
      - General Correspondence, 1970-74 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - 1970 Lease 1660 L Street, NW, Washington, DC, 1968 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - Federal Resources Family Planning Programs & Services, 1969-70 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - Manpower Bill, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - National Legislation, 1969-70 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - New Programs for 1970 (OEO Funds & Affiliates), 1969 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - New Programs for 1970, OEO Appropriations for Family Planning, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - Professionals Involved with Population/Family Planning Problems in Washington, DC Area, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - Program Planning and Development Institute, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - Projects, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - National Headquarters, Washington, DC, Project Developers, 1967-69 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - Project Development
        - Unit Cumulative Report, Third Quarter April 1, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 20)
        - Report, 1973-74 (Box 55, Folder 21)
        - Unit Reports, 1973-74 (Box 55, Folder 22)
      - Project Operations Unit Procedural Manual, May 1970 (Box 55, Folder 23)
      - National Headquarters, Washington, DC, Public Policy Staff, 1969-70 (Box 55, Folder 24)
      - CFPPD Washington, DC Headquarters, Questionnaire on Grants, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 25)
      - National, Washington, DC, HQ Staff Conference at Airlie House, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 26)
      - Regional Family Planning Office DHEW, Region I-X, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 27)
      - Study of 1970-1971 Government Grants to Affiliates, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 28)
      - Title IV's Family Planning Provisions, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 29)
      - Washington, DC, Hougen Lee Visit W/ Dr. Fortescue, Appalachian Regional Commission, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 30)
      - Nestor, Barry, Policy Analyst, 1970-73 (Box 55, Folder 31)
      - Robert Bohlman from 1970 Technical Assistance Consultant, 1970-74 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - National Headquarters, Washington, DC
    - Robert J. Carlson
      - Project Developers, Representative, Midwest, 1967, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 33)
      - Technical Assistant Consultant, 1970-74 (Box 55, Folder 34)
      - Suggestions for Revising the Children's Bureau Guidelines, 1969-70 (Box 55, Folder 35)
    - Robert Crawford
      - Director Technical Assistance, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 36)
      - Chief Project, Developer, Robert D. Crawford, 1967-69 (Box 55, Folder 37)
      - Westinghouse Learning Corporations, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 38)
    - Fisher, Donald, Public Policy Staff Washington DC, 1969-73 (Box 55, Folder 39)
    - Hougen, Lee, Manpower & Department of Labor, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 40)
    - Livengood, Margaret, Consultant, 1970-71 (Box 55, Folder 41)
    - Shalit, Sheldon, Policy Analyst, Washington, DC, 1969-70 (Box 55, Folder 42)
    - Fausto Toscano, Technical Assistant Consultant, 1970-72 (Box 55, Folder 43)
    - Project Developers, F.S. Toscano, Representative SW Area, 1966-1969 (Box 55, Folder 44)
    - Calvin Webb, Technical Assistant Consultant, 1970-73 (Box 55, Folder 45)
    - Weinburg, David, Policy Analyst, 1969 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Community Affairs
    - Burke, Kenyon
      - Correspondence & Memos
        - 1973-74 (Box 55, Folder 47)
        - 1975-77 (Box 55)
      - Newspaper Articles, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 48)
    - Community Relations Program, 1963-66 (Box 55, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, 1970-74 (Box 55, Folder 50)
    - Relations, 1966-69 (Box 55, Folder 51)
    - The Future of the Community Affairs Department, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 52)
    - Memos, Mimeos, General
      - 1970-74 (Box 55, Folder 53)
      - 1975-76 (Box 55)
    - National, General, Mimeos, 1967-69 (Box 55, Folder 54)
    - Grantsmanship Program, 1975-78 (Box 55, Folder 55)
    - History, Responsibilities, Function, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 56)
    - Job Description, 1967-70 (Box 55, Folder 57)
    - Inter-Agency Cooperation, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 58)
    - Medical Rights Fund, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 59)
    - Patient Advisory Committees, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 60)
    - Program & Activity Plan: CY 1976-77 (Box 55, Folder 61)
    - Questionnaires, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 62)
    - Racial & Ethnic Survey, Board & Staff, 1975-77 (Box 55, Folder 63)
    - Community Series, Hall, Lee, Requirements Community Educators, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 64)
    - Wylda B. Robinson
      - Reports, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 65)
      - General Correspondence, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 66)
    - Stewart, Douglas, Press Clippings, 1967 (Box 55, Folder 67)
    - WOMEN'S CAUCUS LEE HALL
      - Hall, Lee, Women's Action Alliance, US National Women's Agenda Coalition, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 68)
      - Women's Advocacy, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 69)
      - Women's Agenda Plan of Action Voluntary Fertilization Control, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 70)
      - Women's Caucus
        - An Introduction, 1975-79 (Box 55, Folder 71)
        - Lee Hall, 1977-79 (Box 55, Folder 72)
        - Member List, 1979 (Box 55, Folder 73)
        - Minutes, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 74)
        - TE & CS Regional Women's Caucus, Minutes, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 75)
        - Three Year Plan 1981-83 (Box 55, Folder 76)
      - US National Women's Agenda, Hall, Lelia V., 1977 (Box 55, Folder 77)
      - Survey of Community Based Family Planning Centers, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 78)
    - YOUTH AND STUDENT AFFAIRS
      - College Program Alternative Budget, 1970-75, circa 1970 (Box 55, Folder 79)
      - Birth Control Information on Campus, Reprint by the College Program, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 80)
      - College Program
        - Campus Birth Control Clinics Reports, General, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 81)
        - Campus Contraceptive Services, 1971 (Box 55, Folder 82)
      - Youth & Student Affairs
        - Conferences on Early Childbearing & Unwed Parenthood (Technical Proposal) and a Business Proposal 1978 (Box 55, Folder 83)
        - Correspondence, 1976-78 (Box 55, Folder 84)
        - DHEW, Programs for the Prevention of Adolescent Pregnancies, 1976-77 (Box 55, Folder 85)
      - Annual Reports
        - 1972-74 (Box 55, Folder 86)
        - 1975-78 (Box 55)
      - Formerly College Program
        - 1970-74 (Box 55, Folder 87)
        - 1975 (Box 55)
    - College Program
      - 1969 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - American College Health Association /PPWP, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - Cornell College Population Study Questionnaire, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Youth & Student Affairs, Establishing Contraceptive Service, University of Maryland, undated (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - College Program
      - Film for PPWP College Program, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Programs for Girls Under 18 Can Consent to Birth Control, Reprint, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Youth & Student Affairs
      - General, 1977-78 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Job Description, Director, Vadies G., 1977 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - College Program
      - Job Description, Regional Coordinater, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - National College Health Survey PP-WP & ACHA, 1972-72 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Objectives & Projections, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Youth & Student Affairs, Program and Activity Plans, CY, 1976-77 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Rape Crisis Centers, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - College Program
      - Report of NYU Birth Control Clinic, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Sex on the Campus & College Health Service, Guttmacher Vadie, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - "Sexual Ignorance Isn't Bliss" by Gene Vadies, Temp Folder, circa 1971 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Summary of Activities & Development of College Programs, 1969 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Sex & Pregnancy Counseling, A Challenge for Hotlines, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Teach-ins, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Field Department, Abortion
    - Evaluation of Clinics & Referral Agencies, 1970-73 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Guidelines for Pregnancy Counseling, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - How to Establish a Pregnancy Counseling Service, 1970 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Inception, Early Goals and Accomplishments, Pregnancy Counseling & Abortion Services, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Job Description, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Legal fees for Defense and Implentation of Abortion Law, Temp Folder (out) (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Population Attitudes Study Commissioned by WNBC TV 4, undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - National Pregnancy Counseling & Abortion Services Program Description, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - New York State Abortion Study, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Pregnancy Counseling & Abortion Referral Questionnaire, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Preterm, Washington, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Policy Statement on Abortion, 1971-72 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Projects, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Youth & Student Affairs, Atlanta Conference, Evaluation Tally Sheet, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Education Department, Youth & Student Affairs
    - Background Paper, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - California Conference, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Handbook: How to Conduct a Conference, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - KC Conference Report, Agenda, etc., 1977 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - KC Evaluation, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - RAC, Kansas City, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Conference Speakers, Memos, KC, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - RAC, Memphis, 1977 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Conference, Monterey
      - 1977-78 (Box 56, Folder 42)
      - Speakers, Part, 1977-78 (Box 56, Folder 43)
      - RAC, 1977-78 (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Quarterly report/ Final report, 1977-79 (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - RAC, Washington DC, 1977-78 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Field Department, Abortion
    - Women's Center Misuse of PP Name, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - Medicaid
      - 1971-74 (Box 56, Folder 48)
      - 1975 (Box 56)
    - Services & Pregnancy Counseling, 1970-73 (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - Abortion Referral Legality, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 50)
    - Referral Liability, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - Request for Information, Misc, 1970-72 (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - Abortion Services in Florida, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 53)
    - Abortion Service Questionnaire, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 54)
    - Commercial Referral Agencies, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 55)
    - Committee for a Legal Abortion/Coalition for a Free Choice, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 56)
    - Proposed Guide to Abortion Facilities, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 57)
    - Requests for a Policy Statement on Abortion, 1970-72 (Box 56, Folder 58)
    - Requests for Information, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 59)
    - Revision of Abortion Referral Records, Request for Information & Comments, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 60)
    - The Shirley Wheeler Case, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 61)
    - Survey Correspondence, 1970-72 (Box 56, Folder 62)
    - Reproductive Services, Temporary Folder, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 63)
    - Survey of Affiliate Abortion, Related Activities, 1970-72 (Box 56, Folder 64)
    - Survey, Affiliates 1970, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 65-66)
    - Survey of Abortion Referrals in Texas Affiliates, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 67)
    - Top Priority Projects, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 68)
    - Buckner, Nancy
      - Technical Assistance, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 69)
      - Correspondence & Memos, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 70)
    - PP Association of the Atlanta Area, 1970-71 (Box 56, Folder 71)
    - Susan Dickler
      - Correspondence & Memos, 1971-73 (Box 56, Folder 72)
      - Workshops, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 73)
    - National Pregnancy & Abortion Counseling, East Coast, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 74)
    - East Coast Pregnancy Counseling
      - Information & Referral, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 75)
      - Workshops
        - Niagara Falls, Canada, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 76)
        - Charlotte, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 77)
        - Sarasota, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 78)
        - General, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 79)
      - Physician Training, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 80)
    - Mid-Continent Pregnancy Counseling & Abortion Project
      - General, 1971-73 (Box 56, Folder 81)
      - Workshop, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 82)
      - Information & Referral, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 83)
      - Task Force Meeting, 1972-73 (Box 56, Folder 84)
      - Conferences, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 85)
    - Mid-continent Physician Training Workshops, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 86)
  - Francine Stein
    - Field Staff, 1970-71 (Box 56, Folder 87)
    - Field Department Abortion
      - Hospitals, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 88)
      - Preterm Mass
        - 1973-74 (Box 56, Folder 89)
        - 1975 (Box 56)
  - National Pregnancy Counseling and Abortion Services Final Report, 1971 (Box 56, Folder 90)
  - Field Department, Administrative Assistants Workshop Austin, TX, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Field Services
    - Adoption Correspondence
      - 1971-74 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - 1975 (Box 57)
    - Affiliate Employment Opportunities, 1969-71 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Field Department
    - Affiliate Federal Projects Evaluation and Review Questionnaire, 1969-70 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Field Activities During, 1970-71 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - National
    - Field Assistance Plan Formerly "Big Sister Plan," 1959-64 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - "Big Sister" Plan, 1956-64 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Whitmore, George D., Correspondence, Memos, Staff, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Field Department
    - Mrs. Helen Brooks' (England) Visit to Affiliates (Itinerary), 1971 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Committee Meeting Chicago, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Community Development Foundation, Correspondence, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Day Care Centers, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Field Calendar, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Functional Allocations, 1971-72 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Goals for the Provision of Contraceptive Service, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Group Purchase Clinic Supplies, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Affiliate Handbook, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - General History, Duties Field Consultants, etc., 1950-64 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Interdepartmental Comm. on Field Service, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Interoffice Correspondence, 1964-70 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Internship Program, 1970-74 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - List of Dates, Meetings, 1971-72 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Memos, Mimeos General, 1970-74 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Memorial Gifts (Temporary Folder), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Memos to Affiliates, Ex Directors & Presidents, 1964-69 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - PD-5 Procedures, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - PP Affiliates, Pill Research, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - PPWP Handbook Correspondence, 1971-72 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Field Department Plan, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - PP/WP as a Purchasing Agent for the Affiliates (Bulk Purchase Contracts), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Planned Parenthood Training Centers, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Position Paper on Staff Development PPWP, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Problem Solving Sessions, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - Proposed Organizational Charges, Field Department with Reduction in Budget, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Outreach Program, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - National Reports, 1959-68 (Box 57, Folder 36-37)
    - Reporting on Non-Contraceptive Services, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 38)
    - Report on the Review of Training Centers, Wylda B. Robinson, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - National, Field Study Committee, Correspondence, 1955-56 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Field Department
    - Field Staff Meetings
      - 1976-77 (Box 57, Folder 41-42)
      - Troika Meetings, 1973-74 (Box 57, Folder 43)
      - 1973-74 (Box 57, Folder 44)
      - McAllen, TX, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 45)
      - Houston, TX, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 46)
      - Atlanta, GA, 1972-73 (Box 57, Folder 47)
      - New York City, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 48-49)
      - 1972 (Box 57, Folder 50)
      - Austin, TX, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 51)
      - Kansas City, MO, 1971 (Box 57, Folder 52)
      - McAllen, TX, 1970-71 Canceled (Box 57, Folder 53)
      - Galena, IL, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 54)
      - Yarmouth and Portland, 1970 (Box 57, Folder 55)
      - Chicago, IL, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 56)
    - National Staff Meetings
      - 1958-74 (Box 57, Folder 57)
      - 1975 (Box 57)
    - Program & Activity Plan: CY, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 58)
  - REGIONAL
    - National, Regional, Affiliates Training Program, 1965-67 (Box 57, Folder 59)
    - Field Department Regional General Correspondence, 1970-72 (Box 57, Folder 60-61)
    - National, Regional, General Correspondence 1964-69 (Box 57, Folder 62-66)
    - Field Department, Regional Financial Statements, 1969-70 (Box 57, Folder 67)
  - National, Regional, Miscellaneous Mimeos, General
    - 1964-74 (Box 57, Folder 68)
    - 1975 (Box 57)
  - National
    - Regional Meeting, Airlee House, VA, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 69)
    - Regional & Representatives, Meetings, Dallas, TX, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 70)
  - Field Department
    - Regional Office
      - Consultation Visits, Naomi Gray, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 71)
      - Organizational Charts, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 72)
    - Regional Workshops Calendar